Jew Larbi Danquah

Accra, Ghana Phone: +233265865717 E-mail: jwlarbi15@gmail.com

Objectives

Aim to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies, frameworks, and programming languages. Commit to expanding your skillset to remain relevant in the ever-evolving tech landscape.

Strive to become an expert in your chosen programming languages and technologies. Master core concepts, best practices, and design patterns to write clean, efficient, and maintainable code.

Education

BSc Physics and Computer Science

Experience

Frontend Engineer (08/2023 – 08/2023) OPOS Hackathon (Nigeria)

- Translated UX and business requirements into elegant code solutions.
- Coded using React, Typescript and Tailwindcss to develop features for both mobile and desktop web platforms.

Frontend Engineer (05/2023 – 06/2023) AlphaX (Accra,Ghana)

• Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.

• Integrated enhancements into web design to improve user stickiness, smooth functionality, and boost load times.

Full Stack Developer (07/2023 – 08/2023) JechTech Inc (Accra, Ghana)

- Developed functional databases, applications and servers to support websites on back-end.
- Developed unit test cases for testing and automation.
- Used NodeJS, ORM and SQL/No-SQL to develop and manage databases.

Skills

- ▶ HTML
- CSS
- TailwindCSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- ReactJS
- Framer Motion
- Next|S
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Jest
- Postgresql
- MongoDB
- Solidity
- Hardhat
- Python